A Guide to the United Daughters of the Confederacy Virginia Division Records, 1901-1949
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
United Daughters of the Confederacy Virginia Division Records, 1901-1949
The Library of Virginia
21706
5.575 cu. ft. and 16 boxes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. E. R. Perkins (21706), Richmond, Virginia; Mrs. C. W. Schaadt (21821), Richmond, Virginia; Mrs. F. J. Pease, F. J. (22283), Richmond, Virginia; Mrs. Langhorne Jones (22646), Chatham, Virginia; Mrs. James S. Moffatt (22756), Lexington, Virginia; Nellie Bosquet (23489), Richmond, Virginia; Virginia Division, United Daughters of the Confederacy (30521), Richmond.
Historical Information
The Virginia Division of the United Daughters of the Confedery was organized on 21 October 1895 as the Daughters of the Confederacy in Virginia. On 1 July 1896, it became known as the United Daughters of the Confederacy, Grand Division of Virginia. On 20 May 1903 it became the United Daughters of the Confederacy, Virginia Division.
Scope and Content
Records of the Virginia Division of the United Daughters of the Confederacy divided into three series. Series I: Grave Marker Applications containing applications for markers for the graves of Confederate soldiers compiled by chapter and by locality, also including correspondence, rosters and histories of various Confederate regiments and companies, biographical sketches, reports, and other chapter papers; Series II: Southern Cross of Honor Applications for Confederate veterans and including lists of recipients; and Series III: Cross of Military Service Applications for descendants of Confederate veterans who served in the Spanish American War, the Philippine Insurrection, World War I, and World War II and including lists and correspondence relating to both the Cross of Military Service and the Southern Cross of Honor.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Grave Marker Applications.
Series II: Southern Cross of Honor Applications.
Series III: Cross of Military Service Applications.
Contents List
- Series I: Grave Marker Applications., 1905-1942., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 1-8)
  Grave Marker Applications containing applications for markers for the graves of Confederate soldiers compiled by chapter and by locality, also including correspondence, rosters and histories of various Confederate regiments and companies, biographical sketches, reports, and other chapter papers.
  alphabetical
  - Subseries 1: Chapters, 1905-1942., 4 boxes (Box 1-4)
    - 13th Virginia Regiment chapter (Orange) applications, 1930-1939. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agnes Lee chapter (Franklin) applications, 1938. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Albemarle chapter (Charlottesville) applications and rosters of grave markers, 1941. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Amelia chapter (Amelia) applications, 1940. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anne Eliza Johns chapter (Danville) applications and rosters of grave markers, 1938, 1941. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Anna Stonewall Jackson chapter (Abingdon) applications, 1941. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Appomattox chapter (Appomattox) applications, 1934, 1936. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Armistead-Goode chapter (Chase City) applications, 1932-1940. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bethel chapter (Newport News) applications, 1939-1940. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Big Stone Gap chapter (Big Stone Gap) applications, 1940. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bowling Green chapter (Bowling Green) applications, 1934. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Breckenridge chapter (New Market) applications, 1931-1937. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Brunswick chapter (Lawrenceville) applications, 1931-1933. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Buckingham chapter (Buckingham) applications, 1930-1932. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - C. R. Mason chapter (Fishersville) applications, 1938. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Captain B. F. Jarratt chapter (Jarratt) applications, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 16.)
    - Captain Sally Tompkins chapter (Mathews) applications, 1931-1932. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Centreville Ridge chapter (Centreville) applications, 1939. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Chesterfield chapter (Chester) applications, 1930-1939. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Chesterfield chapter (Chester) applications, 1932-1941. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Chesterfield chapter (Chester) applications, 1935-1936. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Clarksville chapter (Clarksville) applications, 1930-1931. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Craig chapter (New Castle) applications, 1932-1933. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Elliott Grays chapter (Richmond) applications, 1928-1931. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Elliott Grays chaper (Richmond) applications, roster of grave markers, and history of the Elliott Grays chapter, 1933-1941. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Elliott Grays chapter (Richmond) applications, 1926-1936. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Farmville chapter (Farmville) applications, 1938. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Fluvanna chapter (Palmyra) applications, 1940. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Fredericksburg chapter (Fredericksburg) applications, 1930-1938, 1941. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Greenville chapter (Emporia) applications, 1931. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - H. A. Carrington chapter (Charlotte Court House) applications, 1930-1931. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hampton chapter (Hampton) applications, 1930-1939. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hanover chapter (Ashland) applications, 1930-1938. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Harrison Harwood chapter (Charles City) applications, 1932-1940. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Highland chapter (Monterey) applications, 1941. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hope Maury chapter (Norfolk) applications, 1939-1941. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - James A. Crawford chapter (Goshen) applications, 1934. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Janet Randolph chapter (Richmond) applications, 1939-1940. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - J.E.B. Stuart chapter (Staunton) applications, 1940. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Kirkwood Otey chapter (Lynchburg) applications, n.d, 1940. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Lancaster chapter (Lancaster) applications, 1939, 1941. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Lee chapter (Richmond) applications, 1930-1940. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Loudoun chapter (Leesburg) applications and roster of grave markers, 1930-1940. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Manassas chapter (Manassas) applications, 1939. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mary Custis Lee (Lexington) applications, 1930-1938. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Mary Custis Lee chapter (Lexington) applications, 1931-1940. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mary Custis Lee chapter (Lexington) applications, 1934-1936. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - McComas chapter (Pearisburg) applications, 1931-1939. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - McComas chapter (Pearisburg) applications, 1939-1941. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - McComas chapter (Pearisburg) applications, 1936. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mildred Lee chapter (Martinsville) applications, 1939-1941. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Mineral chapter (Mineral) applications, 1934-1941. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Mount Jackson chapter (Mount Jackson) applications, 1932. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - New Kent chapter (Barhamsville) applications, 1939. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - New River chapter (East Radford) applications, 1936. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Old Dominion chapter (Lynchburg) applications, 1936-1939. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Old Dominion Dragoons chapter (Hampton) applications, 1935-1937. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Petersburg chapter (Petersburg) applications and rosters of grave markers, 1933-1941. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Pickett Buchanan chapter (Norfolk) applications and roster of grave markers, 1937, 1940-1941. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Powhatan chapter (Powhatan) applications, 1938-1939. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Prince George chapter (Hopewell) applications, 1941. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Pulaski chapter (Dublin) applications, 1935-1941. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Radford chapter (Radford) applications, 1939. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Richmond chapter (Richmond) applications, 1936, 1941. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Robert E. Lee chapter (Belle Haven) applications and rosters of grave markers, 1940. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Sally Tompkins chapter (Gloucester) applications, 1940. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Saltville Preston chapter (Saltville) applications, 1934-1936, 1938. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Salyer Lee chapter (Norton) applications, 1937. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Scottsville chapter (Scottsville) applications, 1931, 1940 (one labeled Scottsville or Fluvanna chapter). (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Shenandoah chapter (Woodstock) applications, 1930-1938. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Simeon Walton chapter (Onteria) applications, n.d.. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Southern Cross chapter (Salem) applications, 1934-1936. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Stonewall Camp chapter (Portsmouth) applications, 1939. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Stover Camp chapter (Strasburg) applications, 1939-1940. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Suffolk chapter (Suffolk) applications, 1931-1933, 1939. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Turner Ashby chapter (Harrisonburg) applications and roster of grave markers, 1932-1940. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - William R. Terry chapter (Bedford) applications, 1931-1937. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - William R. Terry chapter (Bedford) applications and rosters of grave markers, 1930-1941. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - William R. Terry chapter (Bedford) applications, 1934-1936. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - William Watts chapter (Roanoke) rosters of grave markers, n.d.. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Williamsburg chapter (Williamsburg) applications, 1940. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Wythe Grey chapter (Wytheville) applications, 1931. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Highland chapter (Franklin, West Virginia) applications, 1938. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Wilkes Valley Guards chapter (North Wilkesboro, North Carolina) applications, 1939. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Confederate rosters, cemetery records, 1905-1931. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Confederate rosters. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Confederate rosters, sketches of organizations, reports. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous reports, correspondence, poem. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sketches of battles and Confederate organizations. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Biographical sketches of Confederate officers and soldiers. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, reports, sketch of Mahone's Brigade. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Localities, 1926-1941., 4 boxes (Box 5-8)
    - Correspondence, 25 June 1926-12 December 1933. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 6 January 1934-13 June 1941. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Confederate grave marker chapter reports. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Albemarle County. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Amelia County. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Appomattox County. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bedford County. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Brunswick County. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Buchanan County. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Buckingham County. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Charles City County. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Charlotte County. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Chesterfield County. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Craig County. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Fluvanna County. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Gloucester County. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Greenville County. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hanover County. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Highland County. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Isle of Wight County. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster County. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Loudoun County. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Mathews County. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - New Kent County. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Orange County. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Powhatan County. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Powhatan County. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Pulaski County. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Shenandoah County. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Warren County. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Wythe County. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Abingdon. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Belle Haven. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Big Stone Gap. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Bowling Green. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Boydton. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Chase City. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Clarksville. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Centreville. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Danville. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Farmville. (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Fisherville. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Franklin. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Fredericksburg. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Hampton. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Harrisonburg. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Jarratt. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Lexington. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lynchburg. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Manassas. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Martinsville. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mineral. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Mount Jackson. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - New Market. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Newport News. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Norton. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Onteria. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Pearisburg. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Petersburg. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Portsmouth. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Radford. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Richmond. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Roanoke. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Salem. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Saltville. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - South Richmond chapter, A-F. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - South Richmond chapter, G-P. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - South Richmond chapter, R-Y. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Staunton. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Strausburg. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Suffolk. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Williamsburg. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Wytheville. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous grave markers. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Confederate dead in various cemeteries. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Civil War period letters and history of individual battles. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Confederate companies--soldier rosters--Cavalry. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Confederate companies--soldier rosters--Artillery. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Confederate companies--soldier rosters--Infantry. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Confederate companies--soldier rosters--counties and cities. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Confederate camp rosters. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Series II: Southern Cross of Honor Applications, 1901-1940., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 9-10)
  Southern Cross of Honor Applications for Confederate veterans and including lists of recipients.
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: A. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Ba-Bl. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Bo-By. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Ca-Cl. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Co-Cu. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: D. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: E. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: F. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: G. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Ha. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: He-Hu. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: I. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: J. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: K. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: L. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Ma-Me. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Mi-My. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: N. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: O. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: P. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Q. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: R. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Sa-Si. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Sk-St. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: T. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: U. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Wa-Wh. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Wi-Wy. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: Y. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Southern Cross of Honor, surname: unidentified. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Southern Cross of Honor records of recipients, 1910-1929. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Southern Cross of Honor records of recipients, 1930-1933. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Southern Cross of Honor records of recipients, 1934-1936. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Southern Cross of Honor records of recipients, 1937-1940. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Southern Cross of Honor correspondence and blank forms 1921-1937. (Box 16)
- Series III: Cross of Military Service Applications, 1928-1949., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 11-16)
  Cross of Military Service Applications. 1928-1949, for descendants of Confederate veterans who served in the Spanish American War, the Philippine Insurrection, World War I, and World War II and including lists and correspondence relating to both the Cross of Military Service and the Southern Cross of Honor.
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ac-Ag. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Al-At. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ba. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Be. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Bi-Bl. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Bo. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Br. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Bu. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ca. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ch-Cl. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Co. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Cr-Cu. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Da-De. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Di-Do. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Dr-Du. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: E. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Fa-Fe. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Fi-Fl. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Fo-Fu. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ga-Gl. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Go. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Gr-Gw. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ha-Harp. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Harr-Hay. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: He-Hi. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ho. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Hu. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: I. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ja-Jen. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Jett. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Jo. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Jones. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: K. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: La. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Le. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Li-Lu. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ma. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Mc. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Me. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Mi. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Mo. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Mu-My. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: N. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: O. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Pa. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Pe-Pi. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Po-Py. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Q. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ra-Rh. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ri. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ro-Ru. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Sa-Sh. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Si-Sl. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Sm-So. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Sp-Ste. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Sti-Sy. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Ta-Te. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Th. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: To-Tr. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Tu-Ty. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: U. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: V. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Wa. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: We. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Wh. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Wic-Williams, Edward. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Williams, John Bell-Willis. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Wiltshire-Win. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Wood-Woods. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Woodson-Wy. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Cross of Military Service, Surname: Y. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Index of award recipients by chapter. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous papers. (Box 16, Folder 11)